{"data":[{"question":"Little Johnny to the neighbour: \"I'm not proud of what I have done.\"     -> Little Johnny admitted .................................................","answer":"he wasn't proud of what he had done","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"Mrs Mitchell: \"I am fond of music and I don't mind Morris dancing.\"    -> Mrs Mitchell told me .........................................Morris dancing.","answer":"she was fond of music and she didn't mind","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"\"Our selling figures are dropping rapidly!\" - said the company manager.     -> The company manager shouted that ........................................","answer":"their selling figures were dropping rapidly!","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"The secretary: \"I can't find these documents but I'm sure they are somewhere here.\"     -> The secretary explained .........................................................","answer":"she couldn't find those documents but she was sure they were somewhere there","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"Garry: \"My parents have been married for twenty-seven years and it's their wedding anniversary today.\"     -> Garry told us .................................................................","answer":"his parents had been married for twenty-seven years and it was their wedding anniversary that day","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"Martha: \"Alison had worked for this firm long before I came here.\"    -> Martha agreed that ................................................","answer":"Alison had worked for that firm long before she had come there","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"\"We must phone Kate\" - said Mark.     -> Mark said ..................................","answer":"they had to phone Kate","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"\"It's still early and you don't have to drive so fast\" - Becky told me.     -> Becky told me ..................................drive so fast.","answer":"it was still early and I didn't have to","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"\"If you hope for promotion, you'll have to be much more active than now'' - the boss said to Jake.     -> The boss explained Jake that .......................................................","answer":"if he hoped for promotion, he would have to be much more active than then","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"},{"question":"\"I can't believe he's leaving me like this\" - cried Sally.     -> Sally cried that ........................................","answer":"she couldn't believe he was leaving her like that","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"63","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"4"}]}